要是我们的鸡和鸭生小宝宝不是很有趣吗
Hey, wouldn't it be cool if our duck and our chick had a little baby?
可以叫他查克
We could call it Chuck.
或狄克
Or Dick.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我要请你们帮忙
Listen, I need a favor.
我刚才在洗澡 正在…
I was in the shower, and as I was...
冲洗时 我感觉到点东西
...cleansing myself, I, uh... Well, I felt something.
很像打喷嚏 但是感觉更爽
Was it like a sneeze, only better?
不是 是我身上长了东西
No, no. I mean, like, a thing on my body.
什么东西
Well, what was it?
不知道 它长在我不能…
Well, I don't know. It's kind of in a place that's not...
我看不到 我想麻烦你们…
It's not visually accessible to me. And I was hoping maybe you guys...
帮我看一下
...could help me out.
不要
Whoa! No.
拜托 又没什么
Come on, you guys. It's no big deal.
嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
是什么 是痣吗
Well, what is it? Is it a mole?
不是 太皱了 不是痣
No, it's too wrinkly to be a mole.
那是青春痘吗
Ew. Is it...? What, a pimple?
不是 它…
No, it's...
比青春痘更高档
...fancier than a pimple.
- 你就去看医…   - 你们在干……
- Look, Ross, just go see a doc...     - Guys, what's...?
确定了 冬天还有两星期
Okay, well, it's definite. Two more weeks of winter.
没错
Yeah, right.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
这是咖啡厅 我都在这里表演
And, um, this is the coffeehouse. This is where I play my music.
- 不错   - 他们是我的朋友
- Good deal.     - Yeah, and these are my friends.
各位 这是文斯 文斯 我的朋友们
People? This is Vince. Vince, the people.
嗨
Hi.
- 嘿   - 文斯是消防员
- Hey.     - Vince is a fireman.
你从燃烧的大楼里救过人吗
Wow. Have you ever rescued anyone from a burning building before?
九十八次 队里第一
Ninety-eight hot saves. Highest on the force.
要是乔伊和我玩火柴
Well, you know, if Joey and I play with matches...
就可以让你累积到一百
...we could get you up to an even 100.
孩子 不能拿火灾开玩笑
Fire safety is not a joke, son.
你说得对 我知道
You're right. I know.
我要走了 晚上要值班
Look, I gotta go. I'm on call tonight.
- 星期六见   - 好
- See you Saturday.     - Okay.
菲比 他好可爱
Wow, he's cute, Pheebs.
但你不是刚和那个幼雅园老师开始交往吗
But I thought you just started dating that teacher.
- 杰森   - 是啊
- Oh, Jason?     - Yeah.
我们晚上要见面
Uh-huh. We're seeing each other tonight. Ahem.
菲比
Well, Pheebs?
一天约两个人 你不像这种人
Two dates in one day? That's so unlike you.
我知道 我只是喜欢拈花惹草而已
I know, I know. I'm, like, playing the field, you know?
我在玩弄别人 三心二意
I'm juggling two guys. I'm sowing my wild oats, you know?
我是三心二意的花心大萝卜
You know, this kind of, like, you know, oat-sowing, field-playing juggler.
他们知道对方的存在吗
So, Pheebs, do they know about each other?
狗狗念书时 嘴唇会动吗
Does a dog's lips move when he reads?
他们不知道
Okay, no, they don't know.
- 各位   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hi.
- 怎样   - 医生怎么说
- Well?     - How'd it go at the doctor's?
他说不用担心 是良性的
Well, he said there's definitely nothing to worry about. It's totally benign.
- 是什么   - 他根本说不出来
- Well, what is it?     - He couldn't even tell me.
他只说是一种皮肤异常
He said it was just some sort of skin abnormality.
更糟的是 他说由于无法辨认
And the worse thing is, he said not being able to identify it...
他不愿意为我切除
...he was reluctant to remove it.
你应该去找我的医生
You know what? You should go to my guy.
我带着第三个乳头去找他时…
Because when I went in there with my third nipple...
- 他直接就把它给切了     - 是啊
- ...he just lopped it right off, you know?     - Yeah?
我还蛮幸运的
So I guess I'm lucky.
虽然比不上天生只有两个乳头的人
I mean, not as lucky as people who are born with two nipples.
至少他们知道你长了什么 你的有名字
At least they knew what yours was. You know? Yours had a name.
也许医学界会以你为名
Oh. Maybe they'll name yours after you.
把它叫做罗斯
You know? They'd call it The Ross.
大家会说 "噢 他长了一个罗斯"
And then people would be, like, "Oh, he's got a Ross."
是啊 真酷
Yeah, that'd be cool.
彼特要跟我分手
Pete's breaking up with me.
什么
What?
我刚才听留言
Yeah, I just checked my messages.
他说等他从亚特兰大回来 "我们得谈一谈"
He said that when he gets back from Atlanta, "We need to talk."
- 然后呢   - 就这样
- And?     - Well, that's it.
没有人会说我们得谈一谈 除非是坏事
People never say, "We need to talk," unless it's something bad.
那不一定代表他要跟你分手
Whoa. That doesn't necessarily mean he's breaking up with you.
- 是啊   - 真的
- Yeah.     - Really?
也许他只是劈腿
Yeah. Maybe he just cheated on you.
这么做不会让我变富裕 但我还是很高兴
And I know I'll never get rich doing it, but I gotta tell you, it's pretty cool...
我正在改变一个孩子的人生
...knowing you're making a difference in a kid's life.
真好
That is so great.
天哪
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
- 赶快通知消防队   - 不
- Uh, we'd better call the fire department.     - No. No.
- 不   - 不必找消防员吧
- No, no?     - Well, we don't need a fireman.
应该找好的技工来
We need, like, a good mechanic.
他们来了 快走
Oh, my God. Here they come. We gotta get out of here.
等一下 为什么
Wait. Why?
要是我想看消防员 我会找消防员约会 好吗
Look, if I wanted to see a fireman, I would date one, okay?
只是一个多出来的乳头
That's all it is, a third nipple.
很普通的第三个乳头
You know? Just your run-of-the-mill third nipple. Yeah.
你可以把它切掉 直接切掉
You can take it off. Just slice that baby right off.
把上衣脱掉让我看一下
Take your shirt off and let's see what we're dealing with here.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
让你看那个非常普通 可以直接切掉的乳头
Just showing you my run-of-the-mill, slice-it-right-off third nipple.
这不是第三个乳头
Well, that's not a third nipple.
首先 它长在你的屁股上
First of all, it's on your ass.
不然是什么
Well, then what is it?
等一下
Wait a minute. Hold it.
- 詹森 麻烦来一下   - 我在跟汉弥顿讲话
- Jansen, will you come in here a moment?     - I'm with Hamilton.
他对怪东西很在行 叫他也来
He's good with weird things. Bring him in too.
我得去帮彼特浇花
I gotta go water Pete's plants.
你们知道吗 如果他想分手 我就不浇了
You know what? If he's gonna break up with me, maybe I won't water his plants.
如果他要分手 干脆让乔伊和我去浇
Well, if he's gonna break up with you, maybe Joey and I should water his plants...
懂我的意思吧
...if you know what I mean.
又或者…
Or, ha, ha...
我们可以对着花盆撒尿
...we could go over there and pee on them.
我受不了了
I can't take it, you know?
我好怕会被捉到
I'm always afraid one of them is gonna catch me with the other.
我快疯了
It's making me crazy.
那为什么不跟其中一个分手
Well, honey, why don't you break up with one of them?
你不是在拈花惹草吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What happened to playing the field?
现在不好玩了
Well, it doesn't feel like playing anymore.
比较像工作 很累人
It's feels like work. It's like I'm working in the field.
- 那就选一个   - 对啊 你比较喜欢哪一个
- So, Pheebs, pick one of them.     - Yeah, which one do you like more?
文斯很棒 他是男人中的男人
Well, Vince is great, you know? Because he's, like, a "guy" guy.
他好壮 真的好壮
You know? He's just so burly, so very burly.
好 那就选文斯吧
Okay, good. So there you go. Go with Vince.
但是杰森好感性
Yeah, but Jason's really sensitive.
感性很重要 选他
Well, sensitive is important. Pick him.
是啊 听娘娘腔的话
Oh, sure. Go with the sissy.
杰森才不娘娘腔
Jason is not a sissy.
不是啦 我是说钱德
Oh, no, no, no. I meant Chandler.
我晚上有约
You know, I have dinner plans.
谢谢各位临时赶来
Thank you so much for coming on such a short notice.
各位先生 女士 我行医二十三年
Ladies and gentlemen, I've been practicing medicine for 23 years...
现在却被难倒了
...and I'm stumped.
这里是书房
Okay, this is the den.
你们看 灯光…
All right, check this out. Lights.
少一点光…不好的光
Whoa. All right, less lights. Bad lights.
灯光走开
Lights, go away.
看到了吗 下对指令就行了
Aw, see? You just need to find the right command.
也可以用调的
Yes. And the dimmer switch.
他那么有钱 电视还真小
Whoa. For a rich guy, that's a pretty small TV.
那是视讯电话
No, no, no. That's the videophone.
你们根本不该在这里的 所以不要乱碰东西
But hey, guys, you're not supposed to be here, so please don't touch anything.
宜家家居 好舒服
IKEA, this is comfortable.
这里太高级了
This place is amazing.
- 那个厨房是我见过最赞的   - 我知道
- Oh, God. That is the nicest kitchen.     - I know.
我是说真的
No, no. It's the nicest kitchen.
冰箱还会祝我今天愉快
The refrigerator told me to have a great day.
你们看 百万富翁的支票簿
Look at this, a millionaire's checkbook.
乔伊  把那个放下
Joey, put that down.
天哪 是彼特 快出去
Oh, my God, that's Pete. Okay, get out.
- 视讯电话要怎么接   - 摩妮卡
- How the hell do you answer a videophone?     - Monica?
原来是这样
I guess that's how.
摩妮卡 你好吗
Hey, Monica, how's it going?
呃…很好
Oh, it's good. It's, um... It's good.
我来帮你浇花
Just here, watering the plants.
别忘了瑞秋旁边那一盆
Well, don't forget that ficus over there by Rachel.
钱德在沙发上
Ha. Chandler's on the couch.
我看到他了 你们还真不会躲
Yeah, I see him. You guys are just the worst hiders ever.
- 嗨 彼特   - 你好吗
- Hi, Pete.     - How you doing?
彼特…
Uh, Pete, um...
那天你说要找我谈一谈
The other day when you said you needed to talk...
请问是好消息还是坏消息
...um, just so I know, is it good news or bad news?
好消息 绝对是好消息
Oh, it's good news. No, it's definitely good news.
等一下 有另一通电话
Hold on a second, I have another call.
你好吗
Hey, how's it going?
还是我
No, no, no, it's still me.
我这里有子母画面
No, it's not. I've got picture-in-picture here.
好 我晚点再回你电话
Yeah. Yeah, okay. I'm gonna have to call you back later.
摩妮卡 我在跟你说话 我再回你电话
Monica? You. I'm gonna have to call you back.
好 改天见
Oh. Oh, okay. Um, so I'll see you soon.
- 好 我爱你   - 我爱你
- Okay. I love you.     - I love you.
我们也爱你
We love you too.
好
Okay.
是好消息 是好消息
Well, it's good news. It's good news.
- 你想会是什么好消息   - 你们看
- So, what do you think the good news is?     - Look at this.
他开了一张五万美元的支票 给一位戒指设计师
He wrote a check for $50,000 to Hugo Lindgren's Ring Design.
对不起 你想会是什么好消息
Oh. Sorry. Uh, what do you think the good news is?
天哪
Oh, my.
摩妮卡要嫁给百万富翁了
Monica's gonna marry a millionaire.
赶快打给妈 打给妈
Hey, you gotta get Mom on the phone. Call Mom. Call Mom.
哈罗
Hello?
那是彼特的妈妈
And that's Pete's mom. Ha, ha.
你得办一个主题婚礼
No, Mon, you have to make it a theme wedding.
主题可以是…
And the theme could be:
"看我们多有钱啊"
"Look How Much Money We've Got."
你可以在喜帖里放钱
You know? I mean, you could put money in the invitations.
你可以用钱做成餐具
You could have, like, little-money place settings.
第一道菜可以上钞票沙拉
And, uh, you could start with a money salad.
虽然干了点 但绝对受欢迎
I mean, it'll be dry, but people will like it.
别再说了
Would you stop?
我们才交往两星期 也不知道他会不会求婚
We've only gone out a couple of weeks. We don't know if he'll propose.
他是彼特 跟别人不一样
Yes, but this is Pete, okay? He's not like other people.
你们第一次约会就去罗马
On your first date, he took you to Rome.
对其他男人来说 那是第三 四次约会的事
For most guys, that's like a third or fourth date kind of thing.
如果他要求婚 那就太疯狂了
Well, if that's what it is, then it's crazy.
摩妮卡说得对 这可是婚姻大事
Monica's right. We're talking about getting married here.
她不能太过着急
Okay? She can't just rush into this.
你又懂什么 你娶了一个女同志
Oh, what do you know? You married a lesbian.
我要走了 我要去跟文斯分手
All right. I gotta go. I have to break up with Vince.
所以你选了那个老师
Oh. So you're going with the teacher, huh?
我很喜欢文斯 但杰森好感性
Yeah. I like Vince a lot, you know? But Jason is so sensitive, you know?
长期来说 感性应该比…
And in the long run, I think sensitive is better than having...
这么 这么性感的身材来得好
...just, like, a really, really, really nice body.
杰森 绝对是杰森
Jason. Definitely Jason.
- 祝我好运吧   - 祝好运
- Wish me luck.     - Good luck.
天啊
Oh, my God.
抱歉 我在想像接到钞票抛花的感觉
Sorry. I was just imagining what it'd be like to catch the money bouquet.
（引擎公司）
抱歉 文斯在吗
Excuse me. Um, is Vince here?
在
Oh, sure.
- 文斯   - 来了
- Vince.     - Yo.
你们还会真的滑下来
Wow. I didn't know you guys actually used those.
什么事
So, what's up?
这件事很难敔齿
This isn't gonna be easy. Um...
我们还是别再见面了
I don't think we should see each other anymore.
很好
Good deal.
- 对不起   - 没关系
- I'm sorry.     - No, it's okay.
我还以为我们之间很特别
It's just that, uh, I thought we had something pretty special here.
我以为终于找到可以倾诉的对象
An you know, I felt like you were someone I could finally open up to.
我还有好多事没跟你分享
There's so much in me I haven't shared with you yet.
- 天哪 我不知道你…   - 抱歉 我说不出话来了
- Oh, my God. I didn't know you were so...     - I'm sorry. I can't talk.
我要去写日记
I'm gonna go write in my journal.
等一下
Wait. Wait. Wait.
（中央咖啡厅）
我说了 你如果想解决那个问题 就去找我的药草师
I'm telling you, if you wanna take care of that thing, go see my herbal guy.
谢了 我是想切除 不是想做成香料
Thank you, but I wanna remove it, Pheebs. I don't wanna make it savory.
当女生与长了怪东西的男人睡过后
You know, when girls sleep with guys with weird things on their body...
都会跟朋友讲
...they tell their friends about it.
拿来
Give me that.
别生我的气 但我就是忍不住
Hi. Okay, don't be mad at me, but I couldn't resist.
新娘杂志
Bride's magazines?
我知道你不会答应求婚
Yes, and I know that you said you'd say no if he asked you...
但是穿这套唐娜•凯伦走红毯
...but I'm sorry, how great would you look walking down the aisle...
会有多美啊
...in this Donna Karan?
一定会很美
Oh, you so would.
不结婚也要买
Oh, you should get that anyway.
可以穿去夜店
Well, for clubbing.
真的很奇怪…
It is so weird.
我说过不会答应 但是今天早上…
I know what I said. But, um, this morning...
我躺在床上想像说愿意的感觉
...I was lying in bed, I was imagining what it'd be like to say yes.
我知道有点突然 也很匆促
I know it's a little sudden, and it's rushed...
我也不是会做这种事的人
...and it's totally not like me to do something like this.
但这不意味着我不能做 对吧
But that doesn't mean I can't. Right?
毕竟我那么爱彼特
I mean, I'm crazy about Pete.
我们追求同样的东西
And I know that we want the same things.
当我想到说愿意的感觉…
And when I thought about saying yes...
我觉得很快乐
...it made me really happy.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我知道
I know.
我需要更多派
I need more pie.
要是你真的结婚 我可以带两个人去吗
Hey, Mon, um, if you do get married, can I bring two guests?
你没跟消防员分手
You didn't break up with that fireman?
没有 我的话就是这个意思
No, that was my way of telling you.
其实他非常感性
Well, it turns out he's incredibly sensitive.
他写日记 还画画
He keeps a journal and he paints.
他还为我画了一幅炭笔画
He even showed me charcoal drawings that he drew of me.
他比较想用水彩画 但是黑炭比较容易取得
He'd prefer watercolors, but, you know, he has easy access to a lot of charcoal.
那你要甩掉杰森吗
So then are you gonna dump Jason?
对 我总得跟其中一个分手
Well, yeah, because I have to break up with someone and...
杰森很感性 但文斯也是
Okay, so Jason is sensitive. But now, so is Vince.
而文斯又有身材
Plus Vince has the body. You know?
所以……
So...
这其实只是数学问题
It's really just about the math.
- 杰森   - 请进
- Jason.     - Yeah, come on in.
你在电话里的语气很严肃
Uh, Phoebe, you sounded serious on the phone.
出了什么事吗
Is, uh, anything wrong?
没事
No.
你一定是罗斯
You must be Ross.
- 你好   - 我是萨吉大师
- Hi.     - I am Guru Saj.
老实说 我以前从未找过大师 所以…
Listen, I gotta tell you, I've never been to a guru before, so...
放轻松 我在中美洲念过很好的医学院
Well, relax. If it makes you feel any better, I've attended...
这样你比较安心了吧
...some of the finest medical schools in Central America.
来看看你的皮肤异常吧
Well, then, let's take a look at this skin abnormality of yours.
请坐
Come on, have a seat.
跟我想的一样 是昆度斯
Aha. As I suspected, it's a kundus.
什么是昆度斯
What's a "kundus"?
不知道 昆度斯对你来说是什么
I don't know. What's a kundus with you?
请趴下
Please lie down.
我有一种药膏可以让它缩小
I've got a salve that ought to shrink that right up.
值得一试
Well, I guess it's worth a try.
那当然 效果应该…
Oh, sure. We should see results...
噢 显然不能这么做
Whoa! Clearly not the way to go.
为什么
What? What?
我们似乎惹它生气了
We appear to have angered it.
我们惹它生气了
We? We angered it?
我看到问题在哪里了
Oh. I think I see the problem.
恐怕我们得动用更有力的手段
And I'm afraid we're gonna have to use a much stronger tool.
天啊
Oh, God.
罗斯 它绝对不可能脱落…
Ross, there is absolutely no way this is gonna come off...
除非你开始…
...unless you start to...
怎么了
What was that?
它掉下来了
Well, it's gone.
怎么会
How's that?
被我的手表刮掉了
Got caught in my watch.
嘿
Hey, ha, ha.
灯光
Lights.
浪漫的灯光
Uh, romantic lights.
真棒
Ooh, nice. Ha, ha.
我说过有事情要告诉你
So, uh, there was this thing I wanted to talk to you about.
对喔 我都忘了
Oh, right. I completely forgot about that.
嗯…
Well, uh...
我最近想了很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
我回顾我的人生…
And I look at my life...
是吗
Yeah?
觉得我已经征服了商界
- And I feel like I've conquered the business world.
我已经征服了知识界
And I feel like I've conquered the intellectual world.
现在又拥有世界上最美的女人
And now I have the most beautiful woman in the world.
但是还有一个缺憾
But there's one thing missing.
什么缺憾
What's that?
我该征服体育界了
It's time for me to conquer the physical world.
好
Okay.
摩妮卡 我想成为…
Monica? I wanna become...
终极格斗冠军
...the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
你想做什么
You wanna what?
我想成为终极格斗冠军
I wanna become the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
那是全世界最激烈的体能竞技
It's the most intense physical competition in the world.
在四十九州被禁
It's banned in 49 states.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我的教练霍奇正在教我…
Okay, my trainer, Hoshi, is teaching me...
截拳道和巴西街头搏击
...a combination of Jeet Kune Do and Brazilian street-fighting.
我还请人设计了专用的八角训练场地
I even had my own octagon training ring designed.
所以你找了擂台设计师
And I suppose you used a ring designer for that.
没错
Yeah.
我要你在最前排看我赢得胜利
Monica, I want you there in the front row when I win.
我要你近得可以闻到血腥味
I want you close enough to smell the blood.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我的父母会很高兴
My parents will be so happy.
# 疯狂的内裤 爬上我的屁股 #
# Crazy underwear Creeping up my butt #
# 疯狂的内裤 总是一成不变 #
# Crazy underwear Always in a rut #
# 疯狂的内裤… #
# Crazy underwear #
他来干什么
Oh, no. What is he doing here?
继续唱…
All right, just keep playing, just keep playing.
你会搞定一切 不会有事的
You'll get through this. You'll be fine.
谢谢大家
Okay, thank you.
依照惯例 演唱完不要跟我说话
And as always, no one talk to me after the show.
嘿
Hey.
- 嘿   - 我刚好路过 看到你在表演
I just was passing by and saw you were playing.
你在台上的感觉好棒
This is kind of cool, seeing you up there.
是啊
Well, hey.
哇 搞什么
Whoa, hey, hey.
怎么回事 他是谁
What's going on here? Who's this guy?
我不知道 他突然跑来亲我 快抓住他 文斯
I don't know. He just started kissing me. Get him, Vince.
- 什么   - 什么
- What?   - What?
好吧 我同时跟你们两个交往
Yeah, okay, I've been dating both of you.
这种感觉很差 因为…
And it's been really horrible, because, you know, it's been...
实在很过瘾
...a lot of fun for me.
你们两个我都喜欢
But I like you both...
我不知道该选谁
...and I didn't know how to choose.
对不起 我很差劲 我人格有问题
So I'm sorry. I'm terrible. I'm a terrible person. I'm terrible.
菲比 别这样 没关系
Phoebe, Phoebe. Relax. It's okay. I mean...
我们又没说 只能跟彼此一对一交往
We never said this was exclusive.
我们也是 你别担心
Yeah, neither did we. So give yourself a break.
真的吗
Really?
是啊 我们交往的时间又不长
Yeah, I mean, you know, we haven't been going out that long.
拜托 我们甚至还没上过床
Come on, we haven't even slept together yet. Ha, ha.
你们没有
You haven't?
- 你们有   - 这是你们的问题
- You have?     - Okay, well, this is none of my business.
我真不敢相信 你跟他上过床了
I can't believe this. You slept with him?
我在公园做了烛光晚餐给你啊
Well, I made you a candlelight dinner in the park.
菲比 我替你省点事
You know, Phoebe, I'm gonna make this real easy for you.
幸好没有太难看
Well, that could've been really awkward.
你在公园给他做烛光晚餐
You made him a candlelight dinner in the park?
我也可以为你做…
Yeah, but I can do that for you. I'm gonna do that for you.
我真不敢相信我和一位…
You know, I can't believe I went out with somebody...
在林木区点火的人约会
...who'd actually have an open flame in the middle of a wooded area.
不会有事的
Everything's gonna be all right.
好吗 狄克
Okay, Dick?
你们好 我是萨吉大师
Hello. I am Guru Saj.
他是鸭子吧 否则…
He's supposed to be a duck, right? Because otherwise...
就超出我的能力范围了
...this is way out of my league.
他咳得很严重 兽医治不好
Yeah, yeah. He's got a really bad cough, and our vet, he can't do anything about it.
你有办法吗
Is there something you can do?
我看看
Let me see.
你能让他吃下蝙蝠吗
Do you think you could get him to eat a bat?